
Speaker 1  (00:01)
This system is going to need to be able to deploy Code So code that A faculty member. Builds through the theater. Builder. 

Speaker 1  (00:21)
It's going to need to be able to Be deployed on the site. Through the platform, so instead of And getting deployed through 

Speaker 2  (00:36)
You're 

Speaker 1  (00:37)
Local machine. Kama, it should be able to deploy straight into the environment or the workspace. How does that work? 

Speaker 1  (01:06)
How do you create a web-based platform? To deploy code. 

Speaker 1  (01:25)
How do you? Build with code on a web-based platform. Without needing to access your files. 

Speaker 1  (01:58)
When logging in? It should automatically default to Ian McClure Jr. So that You can see what the The student facing interface would look like When you log in, there should be a dashboard or a homepage where you have quick access to The tools, the builder, your courses and your experiences On the homepage. 

Speaker 1  (02:50)
You can also keep some basic analytics and have advanced analytics. On the On a link There should be a way for you to customize Your user profile to upload whatever you want to upload. To give the system some context for instance. 

Speaker 1  (03:18)
If Ian mcluor is in a fraternity or He wants to go to law school. 

Speaker 2  (03:27)
Or 

Speaker 1  (03:28)
Is from Jefferson County? In, all of those things are automatically included, And in addition He can include any other information that he would want. The system to draw information from So for instance, if he's working on a big project 

Speaker 2  (03:56)
Or 

Speaker 1  (04:01)
A paper for a course. It can all be Collected in a single spawn. Because this is going to be a learning management system The platform will automatically assign you to the courses that you're enrolled in and populate those courses with the materials and tools that are published by And the faculty member for those courses And in addition And there should be a space for students to be able to Upload things that they're working on whether it is reference literature. 

Speaker 1  (04:57)
Ideas for projects, the beginnings of projects. All directly into the interface To serve as A knowledge base. Essentially, each course. 

Speaker 1  (05:25)
It can be completely delicious. Managed from The interface We would have it Link out to Documents as students are working on Their files through OneDrive or share point. 

Speaker 1  (06:14)
Then, when somebody builds a tool for a specific course, or for a specific purpose, the students can very easily integrate it into their workflow. Because all of the course resources and documents are all already available. 

Speaker 1  (07:26)
In regard to the builder screen currently, there is The builder on the far left the preview in the middle, and on the far right is sandy. It would be great if sandy On the builder, screen was acting as The prototype So that in the middle, you can see the preview description of how The Tool is being built, and in sandy, you can see what it's actually doing. I want sandy to have the same look and feel across all of the pages so that it feels like a consistent companion, but on each different page. 

Speaker 1  (08:23)
It has somewhat of a different purpose. That a sister's student in the context of that page. So when you're on the builder page, it assists By acting as a preview or an active deployment of the Preview language. 

Speaker 1  (08:57)
While in a course 

Speaker 1  (09:10)
Yeah, I don't know, maybe that maybe that doesn't make sense. Maybe we can scratch that And I like the way sandy works right now. I love the way that sandy feels like they are constantly there. 

Speaker 1  (09:25)
No, yeah, that's what it is. So on each page, sandy should anticipate the kinds of things that would be helpful in the context of that page. So when you're on the builder tool, sandy could have so on sandy, there are default things that you could consider asking sandy, right? 

Speaker 1  (09:46)
It's like what is module 3 of my tech 100 course etc et cetera. Can it be? Can those recommendations or suggested prompts be customized to the page that the student or faculty member is on such that on the analytics page? 

Speaker 1  (10:05)
It can tell you or on the course page it can tell you Things like or it'll suggest prompts like When is the next assignment due? What does the next quiz cover? Etc. 

Speaker 1  (10:35)
On the profile page, it would say things like I find any new tools that have been published recently. That may be relevant to me. 

Speaker 1  (11:26)
I should burn that. 

Speaker 1  (11:42)
I think maybe there should just be 4. A subcategories at the top of the page, something like explore, build learn 

Speaker 1  (12:05)
And maybe something else, maybe even not. And then within build, you have A builder refiner. 

Speaker 1  (12:26)
Collaborator. A builder essentially is focused on getting the tool out 

Speaker 2  (12:35)
Out of front of it. 

Speaker 1  (12:37)
The person's brain, so if they wanted to quickly come up with A A patient's simulator for Delivering bad news, it would generate a prototype. I'm very quickly. Then, refiner has all of the tools that you have built Organized. 

Speaker 1  (13:16)
In reverse chronological error order Of being modified. Where you can tinker with Those tools that you've built but not published yet Until they are Ready period for collaborator. This is where you could ask for help from the community. 

Speaker 1  (13:43)
Ask for people to The troubleshoot it and provide feedback Unlike for instance, if I wanted other people who are law students to review my cross examiner. App and provide feedback. And then they could do it there. 

Speaker 1  (14:13)
And then finally There's the publish, which is to actually push it out onto the marketplace. 

Speaker 1  (14:44)
Were you building in some tools for both refinery and collaborator? On collaborator maybe there could be A suggestive. Tuul, review. 

Speaker 1  (15:32)
If somebody Has an idea? If somebody is building A A tool they can Request although people to help them out with some kind of currency, you earn the currency through experience points. You gain experience points by being a collaborator by publishing tools by Fine-tuning. 

Speaker 1  (16:24)
And so maybe it's not an xp system. Maybe instead, it's a currency. And you can post bounties. 

Speaker 1  (16:37)
Anne set. A bounty using whatever this currency is Maybe it's sand. Maybe it's just generic credits. 

Speaker 1  (17:05)
I kind of like sand. And the ways that you gain this currency is There are a lot the things that reward you the most are Things like A number of people who download and use your tool Number of A tool. Collaborations that you've reviewed. 

Speaker 1  (18:13)
On the collaborator tool, there should be an AI system that asks questions beyond just rate this thing on a scale, from 1 to 5 Instead, it opens with what did you think? And then has a guided legend. Evaluation of the product With an AI. 

Speaker 1  (19:45)
The question becomes, what do you do with the currency? Eventually, the obvious answer to that is That it's going to be The replacement for money when this becomes a national platform. In the meantime, though, all of the Tools should be available to everyone at the university. 

Speaker 1  (20:11)
And they shouldn't need to pay for any of that. 

Speaker 1  (20:31)
But what do you do until then? How do you use this currency? Is it just for like Avatar? 

Speaker 1  (20:42)
Improvements. 

Speaker 1  (21:00)
Maybe it's build credits. Because building is going to take computation. It's going to take computation to build, and that's how you earn your build credits by giving feedback on other people's Ideas in their projects And by publishing, when you publish As people download your tool 

Speaker 1  (21:43)
Then, you get a certain currency, almost like a paycheck. 

Speaker 3  (24:58)
Please give me. 

Speaker 1  (26:03)
The currency. It can be used to Post bounties, or to You've used Inference or to? Purchase extracurricular or nonproductive. 

Speaker 1  (26:27)
AI powered experiences, more tools. From the sandbox, so things like Your Athletics, tracker or And AI powered. Basketball bracket team. 

Speaker 1  (26:54)
Where you and all of your friends It's set up March madness, brackets. 

Speaker 1  (27:24)
Or some entertaining thing like role playing as Jon Snow from Game of Thrones. And getting to interact with other characters 

Speaker 1  (27:49)
Or little games or puzzles, little logic puzzles All of the ways that people use large language models for entertainment. You could build Tools or experiences that live on the platform. But if it's entertainment Considered then? 

Speaker 1  (28:15)
It costs. Sand or this currency? And the argument is that inference and computation is going to cost some amount of money So if you are using the tool for non educational purposes Then, there should be some amount of a restriction. 

Speaker 1  (28:47)
But also that. I at least at the beginning. It's relatively easy to earn credits like. 

Speaker 1  (28:56)
Let's say you start with a 1000 credits just going through and spending. 5 minutes demoing. Somebody's software would give you Our 4 1000 credits Or anytime somebody downloads and uses your tool That's a 100 credits. 

Speaker 1  (29:35)
What else are there other ways that somebody can earn credits on this system? 

Speaker 1  (31:32)
There should be a university The category for tools, so like if somebody creates A Choose your major or To help with financial aid tolerance That it ends up there. We should also have those Datasets available. So that anyone can build within those Datasets anything that is publicly open. 

Speaker 1  (32:10)
For instance, all of the training data or training material for A financial aid. Advisor or assistant. All of that data should be made available. 

Speaker 1  (32:39)
Similarly, students should have access to Datasets for each of their courses so that they can choose to build each It's something for a specific course and have access to The course material that The professor has chosen to make public Things like the syllabus. And by make public, I mean Publish, as though they were on canvas publishing 

Speaker 1  (33:37)
Can we also build out That tool. To be interviewed. For a podcast. 

Speaker 1  (33:51)
Essentially, what the tool would do is Create a synthetic voice And ask the user questions Let's say that I was teaching fractures. And the questions would be things like, how does bone remodeling happen? Or what is an osteoclite osteocyst? 

Speaker 1  (34:27)
An osteoclast. 

Speaker 1  (35:39)
I think it's important that this thing get access to a bunch of the Azure connectors that are going to be available. Through Copyloot, studio. For instance, if somebody wants to build something, that accesses the internet or Users a speech to text or Text-to-speech They should be able to Access those tools that are available through Azure, to that end on the builder page Can you put a list maybe down at the bottom? 

Speaker 1  (36:32)
Below everything else, a list of the kinds of Azure tools that are available like speech to text etc. Also, when you're using the microfu, the microphone function Can you create the text? Will you output the text into the text box? 

Speaker 1  (37:11)
But not. Send the query and tell the user sends the query And that way, if they get cut off, or if they stumble, or if they want to edit their response or question, they have the opportunity to do that with a keyboard. 
